<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
 <Module>
 <ModulePrefs title="MiniMessage Sample">
  <Require feature="minimessage" /> 
  </ModulePrefs>
 <Content type="html">
 <![CDATA[ 
  <div>
    This is some gadget content here
  </div>

  <!-- Create message within the DOM in order to position dismissible messages -->
  <div id="message">Click on the X to hide</div>

  <div>
    Some more gadget content here
  </div>

  <script>
    var msg = new _IG_MiniMessage(__MODULE_ID__);

    // Case 1: Create dismissible message with an HTML string.
    // Create a quick dismissible message by passing in an HTML string as the first parameter.
    // By default, this message will be inserted at the very top.
    var one = msg.createDismissibleMessage("New message using HTML string");

    // Case 2: Create dismissible message with an existing HTML element
    // Create a dismissible message referencing an HTML element already existing within
    // the DOM.  This will preserve the location of the message allowing the user
    // to position where the message will show.
    msg.createDismissibleMessage(_gel("message"));

    // Case 3: Create dismissible message with an HTML element not yet within the DOM.
    // Some users want/need to generate HTML using W3C DOM methods for various reasons.
    // By default, the message is inserted at the very top.
    var div = document.createElement("div");
    div.innerHTML = "New message created by W3C DOM methods.";
    div.onmouseover = function() {
      div.style.backgroundColor = "green";
    };
    div.onmouseout = function() {
      div.style.backgroundColor = "";
    };
    msg.createDismissibleMessage(div);

    // Case 4: Create a dismissible message with different background color and forecolor
    var colorMsg = msg.createDismissibleMessage("I am unique.");
    colorMsg.style.backgroundColor = "red";
    colorMsg.style.color = "white";

    // Case 5: Create dismissible message with a callback function.
    // Many times, the gadget needs to be notified when a message has been dismissed.
    // If a callback function is defined, it is called when this message has been dismissed.
    // The dismiss can be cancelled if the callback returns false.
    msg.createDismissibleMessage("Execute callback when dismissed.", dismissed);

    // Case 6: Create timer message which dismisses after X seconds.
    // Sometimes, it burdens users to have to click [x] to close a message.
    // With a timed message, you can remove this burden by showing it for a few seconds.
    // When the timer expires, the callback is called if it exists.
    msg.createTimerMessage("<div style='text-align:center;'>Timer message shows for X seconds</div>", 2);

    // Case 7: Create static message which can only be dismissed programmatically by ID.
    // Good for loading messages, where another event will manually dismiss the message.
    var staticMsg = msg.createStaticMessage("Static message.  Manually dismiss by clicking.");
    staticMsg.style.cursor = "pointer";
    staticMsg.onclick = function() {
      msg.dismissMessage(staticMsg);
    };

    // Used as callback function when message is dismissed.
    // If callback returns false, then cancel the dismissal.
    function dismissed() {
      return confirm("Dismiss message?");
    }
  </script>
  

  ]]> 
  </Content>
  </Module>